Guide to the Whitman College Vertical Files
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Lechner, Cynthia (2 Folders)
- Legal Action: Whitman College
- Lee, Arthur
- Lee, Daisy A.
- Lee, Hauton
- Lee, Mabel
- Lee, Robert
- Lee, Walter C.
- Lofia, Marc
- Legge, Theodore W.
- Lehman, Greg Whitman Photographer, pictures, letters (2 folders)
- Lehmann, Donald L.
- Lehrer, Harry
- Leibnitz, Gretal
- Leibnitz, Loretalyn
- Leier, John
- Leitch, Gordon Jr.
- Leming, Reis L.
- Leon, Maria Elena Morales
- Leonard, William Ezekial
- Leonard, William Ramsdell
- Le Roux, Frank
- Lesley, Craig
- Lester, Peter
- Lester, Peter F.
- Levin, Lyolia
- Levinson, Katherine
- Lewin, Michael
- Lewis, Scottye
- Lerenbach, David
- Ley, Robert
- Lillequist, Alice
- Lindenburger, Jason
- Linder, Jon
- Lindman, Erick Leroy
- Lindsay, Steven
- Little, Agnus
- Linquist, Tristram
- Little, Agnes
- Little, William T.
- Lilly, Shauna
- Liu, Qiwu
- Livengood, Charles Alfred
- Lloyd, Fiona
- Lockhart, James S.
- Lohnes, Neta
- Loiland, Harry L.
- Lomanitz, Dr. Ross
- Lomen, Lucille
- Loomer, Kevin
- Loomis, Miriam Lincoln
- Long, Beulah W. (Mrs. Lewis)
- Lopez, Manuel L. (2 Folders)
- Lopez-Adams, Norma
- Lorenz, Carmen
- Loring, Harold A.
- Lovett, David
- Lowden
- Lowe, Leonia
- Lucas, Patricia Latourette
- Luce, Charles
- Ludwig, Clarence Columbus
- Luginbuhl, Martha L.
- Luhn, Mary
- Lund, Philo W.
- Lundquist, Tristrum S.
- Luong, John Trung Kien
- Lutcher, Lewis
- Lyman, John Cushman
- Lyman, James Kerr
- Lynch, Leila "Lee"
- Lynch, Michael
- Rededication of Lyman House
- Lyman House (2 Folders)
- Ma, Glen Y.S.
- MacDowell, Mrs. Edward
- MaCdonald, Virginia Baker
- MacDougall, Sue Ellen
- Mackenzie, Dr. Norman
- Macgowan, Mike
- MacLeod, Alex
- MacMorran, Richard
- Maeno, J. Rey
- Magnuson, H.R. (Ray)
- Main, Jackson Turner
- Mair, Dennis
- Make a Difference Day
- Malde, Robert
- Manley, Donald L.
- Mann, Denise
- Manning, Rob
- Manning, Howard
- Manser, Percy
- Mapson, Frank
- Maps, Campus
- Marcus Whitman Statue for the Alaska-Yukon-Pacific Exposition
- Margenau, Henry
- Markoff, John
- Mariner, William
- Marquis, George
- March, Tim
- Marshall, Albert H.
- Marchshall, Bruce
- Marshall, James
- Marshall, Lew
- Martin, Alvin R. (2 Folders)
- Martin, Douglas E.
- Martin, Helen
- Martin, Howard
- Martin, Ruby E.
- Martin, Suzanne - Lecturer in History and Classics
- Martindell, Jackson
- Mascot information Whitman College: debate, images, clippings
- Mason, Edward
- Mason, Harry M.
- Mastin, David
- Matson, Kathleen
- Matthews, Virginia
- Mattson, Rebecca
- Maxey Hall
- Maxey, Elnora Campbell
- Maxon, Eric
- May, Catherine
- May, David
- May Fetes, Student Life
- May Fete: Knights Whitman Honorary
- May, Lisa
- May, Mae
- May, Michael M.
- McCall, Roy C.
- McBirney, Ruth C.
- McCarthy, James
- McClane, Douglas Valentine
- McClintick
- McClure, Jay
- McClusky, David '94
- McCrunk, Lawrence J.
- McCoy, George T.
- McDonnald
- McDonald, Jack
- MacDowell, Edward
- McFail, Mrs. Charles B.
- McFarlaud, Betty
- McGills, John W.
- McGrath, Robert J.
- McCaw Buildings
- McCulloch, Tara Emerald
- McGraw, JohnHarte
- McGregor, John
- Mcguire, Thomas R.
- McInTyre, Lucile
- McKay, John, Prof.
- McKay, lJoyce
- McKay, Richard
- Mckee, J.A.
- Mckee, Paul Boole
- McKellar, Harold and Helen
- Mckenzie, Robert Arthur
- Mckinney, David
- Mckinnon, Craig
- McLaughlin, Cheryl
- MxLaughlin, The Very Rev. John D.
- McLeod, Alex
- McLeod, James Norman
- McMenemy, Richard A.
- McMillan, Edward
- McMurtrey, Lee
- McNamara, Molly
- McNoughton
- McPherson, Mary Pearl (Kelso)
- McVay, Al
- Mechley, Braden
- Meinig, D.W.
- The Meaning
- Mecca
- Meister, Nancy
- Melchen, John
- Mementos of Student Political Activity
- Men's forum
- Mendenhall, Hallam Evans
- Mendenhall, J. Wesley
- Menard, Scott
- Menefee, Aemiliam F.
- Merz, Sarah
- Messer, Peter
- Messner, Joseph
- Metastasio, Arthur P.
- Metcalf, Harry
- Meyer, Claudia
- Meyer, Herbert L.
- Meyer, Merle Eugene
- Midsummer Musical Retreat
- Miller, Arjay - honorary degree 1965
- Miller, Russell
- Mian, Mary
- Miller, Winlock William
- Mills, Abbott Lowe, Jr.
- Mills, Lester
- Mills, Thelma
- Michaelis, Harley
- Miller, Ernest Gale
- Milne, William Edmund
- Minier-Birk, Sigyn
- Mitchell, Art
- Mitchell, Claire
- Mitchell, Donald V.
- Mitchell, James B.
- Mitchell, Sally Taylor
- Mize, Herm
- Mitchell, Sherma nBaley
- Minnick, Walter Lawrence
- Molohon, Barney
- Molohun, Bernad
- Monahan, Russell D.
- Monson, Judith Louise
- Montgomery, Ann
- Montgomerie-Neilson, Beaumont
- Montgomery, Thomas
- Moody, David R.
- Moore, Edith
- Moore, Sharon
- Monales, Michell
- Mordor
- Morey, Ann Janine
- Morgan, Arthur
- Morgan, Edward Paddock
- Morgan, Esther Cornelison
- Morgan, Gwendolyn J.
- Morris, Lorraine
- Moley, Raymond
- Morris, Pat
- Morrison, Ilabelle S.
- Morton, Karen
- Moskov, Angelo
- Mount, Joe
- Mozer, Paul
- Mr. Whitman Pageant
- Honorary Degrees
- Munns, Frank
- Munson, Sarah
- Murar, Christine
- Murphy, Lawrence Parker
- Murray, Janet
- Myers, Iris Little
- Myers, Robert C.
- Nagle, Betsy
- Nakagawa, Keiichiro
- Nakamura, Rie
- Netting, Nancy Silverman
- Napier, Lori
- Neal, Trevor
- Neher, Richard
- Neher, Edna Sanders
- Neiland, J.D.
- Nelson, Clark
- Nelson, Marjorie M.
- Nelson, Sandra
- Nessel, Margaret "Peggy"
- New Student Book and Community Read Program
- Newcomer, Lloyd R.
- Nielson, Eloise
- Niemi, Fred G.
- Nightingale, Richard Edwin
- Nilssen, Sigurd
- Niven, Lewis hamilton
- Nixon, O.W.
- Noben, Mona
- Noonan, W.E. (2 Folders)
- Nord, David Award
- Nordstrom Family-Friends of Whitman College
- Norling, Ernest
- Norris, Silbert
- Northam, Jeff
- Northrup, Doyle L.
- Northwest Renewable Energy Festival
- Clothing and Dress
- Norsworthy, Claire
- Novikoff, Ivan
- Novakovich, Skip
- NW Assn. Private Colleges and Universities
- Nyman, Steve
- Nyrop, Kris
- O'Reilly, Brian Paul
- O'Reilly, Pat
- Organic Garden
- Organizations and Honoraries
- Owen, Frances
- Owen, Henry
- O'Conner, Mark- Concert at Cordiner Hall
- Odell, Morgan S.
- Odonnell, Ashton J.
- Ojaide, Tanure
- Olin Building
- Oliver, Allan
- Oliver, Patrick
- Opperman, Ilse W.
- Order of Waiilatpu
- O'Reilly, Pat
- Osborn, Sharon Kaufman
- Oswald, Worth
- Pacific Northwest College Congress 1948
- Padfield, Harland
- Pailet, Lenny
- Page, Harold
- Page, Patrick
- Palfin, Richard
- Palmer, Stephanie
- Panzl, Barbara
- Parents Council
- Parents Core Class
- Parents' Clubs
- Parent Loan Program
- Parents Orientation
- Parents' Programs
- Parents of Students
- Parents Weekend
- Parking
- Parker, Alan Dale
- Parkinson, Stephen
- Parkinson, Steve
- Patton, Edith Pope
- Paske, Gerald H.
- Patnode, J. Scott
- Paulson, Allan
- Payne, Ancil H. (former trustee)
- Payne, William H.
- Paynter, Carrol L.
- Peach, Bernard, Writings
- Peach, Bernard
- Pearsons, Daniel Kimball
- Pearson, Daniel
- Peck, Katherine
- Peer, Jose Mario
- Penk, Anna
- Pengra, Marjorie L.
- Prep Band
- Pepoon, Helen Abby
- Perier, Richard
- Peringer Family
- Perlsweig, Judith
- Perrine, John
- Perry, Bill
- Perry, Loyal Iliff
- Perry, Louis
- Peters, Thomas
- Peterson, Alice
- Peterson, Carl
- Peterson, Larry Wayne
- Peterson, Laura
- Peterson, Paul D.
- Peterson, Robin
- Pfuhl, Erdwin H.
- Phelps, Nick
- Phelps, Ruth
- Phillips, Mrs. Andrew J.
- Phillips, Hollibert
- Philip, Myriam
- Phillips (Mills), Pauline (Polly)
- Phelps, Ruth Simpson
- Phillips, Scott
- Phillips, Scott
- Philosophy and Literature Journal
- Phonathon
- Physical Plant
- Picha, Patty
- Pickering, Donald Everett
- Pickett, Susan (2 folders)
- Piger, Gil
- Pitman, Dr. Paul Marsh
- Pirie, Ellen
- Planned Giving
- Platt, Steve Anderson
- Plucker, Charles
- Plummer, Lisa A.
- Plute
- Political Union 1960
- Pope, Edith
- Pope letters (Philip H. Pope)
- Post, Homer Avery
- Post, Tom
- Potter, Jonathan
- Potter, Ralph K.
- Powell, Patty
- Praaken, Donald Wilson
- Pranks
- Pratt, Howard E.
- Pratt, Norma W.
- Pre-Health Services
- President's Home
- Press Club / School of Journalism
- Prentiss Hall
- The President's Association of Whitman College
- President's Gift Society
- Pringle, Bob
- Proctor, William Martin
- Production Services
- Pryor, Nancy
- Pu, Burton
- Pugh, Paul
- Pulfer, Phylis
- Purcell, Gerald
- Quartarone, Rina
- Quast, Werner Carl
- Quinn, Alberta
- Radin, Max
- Rainwater, Pat
- Rambaldi, Marlene
- Ramstedt, John
- Randlett, Mary
- Raschke, Curt
- Rasmussen, Genevieve
- Ravasse, Yvonne
- Ravasse, Paule
- Ravasse, Mille. Paule
- Raykoff, Ivan
- Raymond, Fred M.
- Real Mail
- Reavis, Virginia L.
- Redmau, Thomas O.
- Reed, James
- Reed, Katie
- Reed, Jeffrey Alan
- Reed, Mary E.
- Rees, Denton
- Reeves, John Drummond
- Reid: Photograph
- Reid, Robert, Treasurer 1980
- Reid, Emily Smyder
- Reid, Ross
- Reid, Violet Bowers
- Reister, Lydia
- Rekdal, Thomas Harold
- Remington, Rt. Rev. Wm. P.
- Religion at WC--religious control, church support, Rev. Raymond Brooks
- Renaissance Consort
- Rennewanz, Muriel
- Republican Club
- Retention
- Reynolds, Carrie
- Reynolds Hall (2 Folders)
- Reynolds, Ruth portrait
- Rhodes, Charles E.
- Rhodes, (William) Gale
- Rice, Austin
- Rice, James
- Rich, Sid
- Rich, Theodore R.
- Richards, Amy Belle
- Richards, Bob
- Richards, Bob
- Richards, John
- Richardson, Janet (Mrs. Craig Esary)
- Richarson, Mrs. George F. (Rosella Woodward)
- Richardson, Paul
- Richarson, Phebe
- Riehl, Jack
- Riely (Kraght), Shauna
- Riess, Gordon S.
- Riggs, Susan Marie
- Riley, Walter L.
- Ringhoffer, Herbert
- Ringhold, John R.
- Ritts, Karen
- Ritz, Richard
- Rizzuti, Vincent
- Roberts, Carlisle B.
- Roberts, Kathryn
- Robinson, Annie Rue
- Robinson, Frank Crawford
- Robinson, Dorothy
- Robinson, Scott S.
- Robinson, Scott
- Robinson, William Dunlop
- Rochester, Junius
- Rogers, Mary Fowler
- Rojansky, Vladimir
- Roe, Maurice
- Roehm, Klaus
- Rogers, Samuel G.
- Rolfe, Jan and Phil
- Roosevelt Organ
- Rose Garden, Mother's Rose Gardens, Dedicated 1939
- Roser, Helen Severance
- Ross, Allen
- Ross, Nancy Wilson
- Roth, Neil C.
- Roth, Steven
- Round Table
- Royce, William Stephen
- Roys, Dr. Ralph Loveland
- Ruble, Shirley
- Rublee, Parke A.
- Ruby Edward
- Rudolph, Mikael
- Rupp, Otto Burton
- Rupp, Werner Andrew
- Rubenser, Katie
- Rubey, E.E.
- Rush 1991
- Russo, Jim
- Ruzicka, John Albert
- Ryan, Heber Hinds
- Ryker, George
- Sabbatical Leave
- Salary
- Sakimoto, Susan
- Sakimoto, Phillip J.
- Sample, Laetitia Lillie
- Sampson, Kristin
- Samsoe, Marjorie
- Santler, Sophie
- Sargent, Noel Gharrett
- Sasser, John
- Sato, Tomoko
- Savage, Susan
- Savoie, Denise
- Sax, Kelly
- Saxe, Laura
- Sayre, Jennifer (2 Folders)
- Scarborough, Margaret
- Schwerin, Donald S.
- Scheffler, Thomas J.
- Scheffler, Tom
- Schmidt, Mr. and Mrs. Ted
- Schmidt, Ted
- Schmitt, Carl J.
- Schoessler, David
- Schneider, Lowell E.
- Schneider, Deborah P.
- Schnitz, David F.
- Schoenberg, S. K.
- U-B Progress Edition
- Scholarly Activity Release Time
- Scott, Robert
- Schuette, Jane
- Schweppe, Alfred John
- Schwartz, Orlando
- Schwartz, Karl
- Science: Contributions by Whitman Alumni
- Science Building
- Science Initiative 1999
- Scott, John McCoy
- Scribner, Kevin
- Scuri, Vicki (2 Folders)
- Seal of Whitman College
- Security, Campus
- Security
- Semester in the West
- Senior Class
- Senior Class Gift
- Senior Colloquium
- Senior Fund
- Senior Priviledge 1959
- Service Projects
- Seawell, Oscar
- Setze, Paul J.
- Severance, Mr. H.L.
- Shafer, Diane
- Shaffer, Jack
- Shaffer, Flora Morgan
- Shallbetter, Tami
- Shalom (Hillel Jewish Student Group)
- Sham Rao-Cindy Egolf
- Shannon, Eva
- Shaw, Michael
- Shawe, Victor
- Sheehan Gallery
- Sheldon, James Gail
- Shelmerdine, Cynthia Wright
- Shelton, Holly
- Shepherd, Floyd
- Shepherd, Harold and Helen
- Shepherd, Roxanne
- Sherman, Mike
- Sherman, Stanford
- Sherrod, Shelby
- Sherwood, Marion
- Sherwood Library Display
- Shields, George T.
- Shields, Frederick Sr.
- Shohl, Peter
- Shorey, Denise M.
- Shroer, Norman
- Shoub, Ralph
- Shuman, Mark Samuel
- Sickels, Eleanor Maria
- Signs Senior Gift
- Sill, David
- Silverstein, Todd
- Simcock, Bob
- Simon, Dick Jr.
- Simpson, Milton S.
- Sims, Harold L.
- S.L.I.M.E.
- Skiles, Robbie
- Skillman, Susan M.
- Skipworth, George F.
- Skotheim, Nadine
- Slover, Clark Harris
- Small, Margery Jean
- Small, Mrs. H. H.
- Smith, B. Loyal
- Smith, Edith
- Smith, George
- Smith, Gladys
- Smith, Harold
- Smith, Helen Brebbe
- Smith, Jason
- Smith, Mason
- Smith, Pat
- Smith Philip Mason
- Smith, Philip R.
- Smith, Shannon
- Smith, Verbeck
- Social Circus
- Snapp, Gerry and Dodie
- Snavely, Guy Everett
- Snyder, William Earl
- Soden, James
- Solbach, Vern
- Soper, Dorothy Fox
- Soper, Lee
- Southwick, Kathryn
- Songs, Whitman
- Speakers 1970-
- Speakers 1966-69
- Speakers pre-1965
- Spencer, Omar Corwin
- Sporleader, Marvin
- Stacy-Davis, Thomas A.
- Stacey, Kathlean A.
- Staff (Whitman College)
- Staff at Whitman 1886-1990
- Staff Reduction
- Stafford, Charles F.
- Staines, Russell Burton
- Standlee, Lloyd S.
- Stanton, John
- Starkovich, Stefanie
- Steedman, William S.
- Steele, Cecile (2 Folders)
- Stein, Helen
- Stein, Ida Maria
- Steinback, Curtis
- Steiner, Richard M., The Rev.
- Stenberg, Kathryn
- Stenger, Brad
- Sterling, Odessa Dixie
- Stevens, Robert "Spud"
- Stevens, Nell
- Stewart, Irwin D.
- Stewart, Janet
- Stickles, Mary
- Stimmell, Zenna McLnroe
- Stine, Emma (Mrs. Herbert Gregg)
- Stirling, W.L.
- Stonecipher, Ida Rose
- Stone, Virginia/ Beu, G.
- Storey
- Stephen Ministry
- Storytelling Festival
- Stotsky, Dana J.
- Stradling, John Walter
- Stratton, Dave
- Strong, Curtis Clark
- Stubblefield, Ida
- Stuart, Evelyn Clark
- Stutsman, Harold
- Stuart Wing Dedication
- S.E.F.S.A.
- Student Employment Programs
- Student Evaluation
- Student Exchange, Whitman-High School
- Student Grade Reform Committee
- Student Health: WISH
- Student Life Committee
- Student Life Enhancement Program (in MS office)
- Student Life: Misc. (2 Folders)
- Students Office
- Student Record Book (Unofficial) 1928 - Cornelison Purdy
- The Study Tower
- Summer Programs
- Summer Research Projects
- Student W.E.A.
- Summer Teacher's Program at W.C.
- Summer Institute
- Sundial, Vollmer Court
- SUB Coffee House
- Sullivan, Jerome
- Sumeri, Karin
- Sutherland, Louis C.
- Swain, Mrs. Paul E.
- Symonds, Adam
- Taekwon Do
- Takasawa, Manabu
- Take Back the Night March
- Talent Show
- Tanaka, Helen Kaye
- Task Force on Major
- Tate, Edward Mowbray
- Tatum, Edward L.
- Taylor, Huntington
- Tenure Discussion, 1995
- Tetherow
- Tevis, Minnie May
- Tewinkle, Joseph
- The 3/2 Course Load discussion, 1988
- Theater Productions- Visiting
- Thomas, May K.
- Thomas, Tim
- Thompson, Amy Brown
- Thomason, Calvin Cornelius
- Thomason, Caroline W.
- Thomsen, Robert R. (2 Folders)
- Thompson, Mrs. Tommie-Lou
- Thompson, Dr. W.H.
- Thoraton
- Tieck
- Titus, Charles H.
- Tobin, Gordon R.
- Todd, Laura
- Todd, Otis Johnson
- Todd, Tiger and Mary Wagner (2 Folders)
- Toews, Jim and Debi
- Tompkins, Paul
- Townsend, Talbot
- Towske, Sharon
- Toy, Eckart
- Traut, Herbert Frederick
- Trenholme, Stu
- Trexler, Harrison
- Tucker, Bert H.
- Tugman, Robert
- Tuition Exchange Program
- Turley, William S.
- Turner, Wilma Morton
- Twining, Nathan F.
- Board of Tutors/Tutorig
- Uhlenhopp, Elliott
- Ullman, Al
- Umbaugh, Lillian Merrel
- Unitarian Universalists
- University Exchange
- Urban, Ron
- Usher, Nathaniel
- Utter, John
- Uzzi, Jeannine Asst. Prof of Classics and General Studies
- Valdez, David Michael
- Vandiver, Elizabeth Asst. Prof. of Classics
- Van Patten, William
- Van Sinderen, Steve
- Varsity Ball Queen
- Vernazza, Marcelle Wynn (2 large folders)
- Veterans at Whitman
- Video Conferencing
- Video Editing Facility
- Viebbigs, Joseph Jr.
- Visiting Educators
- Visiting Scholar
- Virgin, Robert
- Visitors Day Materials
- Voice Mail
- Vo, Hong
- Vollendorff, William Sr.
- Vollmer, Mr. J. P. and Mrs. John M. Bonner
- Wade, Jay
- Wade, LeRoy G.
- Wade, Skip
- Waiilatpu
- Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew
- Waite, Anne
- Wakefield, Kathleen
- Wakefield, Walter F.
- Waldo, Jim
- Walker, Fisk Martin
- Walker, Mrs. Gertrude
- Walker, John Turnley
- Walker, Nick
- Walker, Randy
- Walker, Robert
- Wallace, Robert K.
- Wang, Shali
- Warren, Bertram Butler
- Warren, Cliff
- Warren, William C.
- Washburn, Steve
- Washpirg
- Watson, Clarice
- Watts, Sonya
- Weaver, Judge Frank B.
- Wedemeyer, Otto
- Weidig, Marcia D.
- Weiler, C. Susan
- Weir, M. Topology Notes 1966
- Weiser, Eric B.
- Weller, Celia
- Wells, Robert and Maybelle
- Well, Robert H.
- Wells, William Woodraw
- Welty, Isabelle
- Werner, Tim
- West, Adam (notes from speech given here in 1995)
- Western Cluster Pew Science Program
- Westinghouse, Evelyn
- Westwood, Mary
- Wheeler, Adalou
- White, Dori
- White, Mrs, R.B. (Mary Mersereau)
- White, William
- Whitman, Art
- Whitman Direct Action (WDA)
- Whitman Farms
- Whitman Guild
- Whitman in the News and Rankings
- Whitman Overseas Concern in Action
- Whitman Plate
- Whitman to Whitman Run
- Whitman World Hunger
- Widner, Cynthia
- Wilce, Donald
- Wilcox, Mike
- Wilcox, Mike
- Wiley, Martha
- Willcuts, Peggy
- Wilkinson, Vernon Lee
- Williams, Hill
- Williams, Jan
- Williams, Jeanne
- Williams, Luther N.
- Williams, Marvin, M.D.
- Willis, Dr. Park Weed
- Willoughby, Colleen
- Wilson, Irene
- Winchester, Mary Catherine Severance
- Winkler, Andrea Leslie
- Winter Solstice Celebration
- W.I.S.E. (wise)
- Wissenback, Dottie
- Wolter, Diemut
- Wolverton, James
- Wong, Trevor K.
- Wood, Allan
- Woody, Ken
- Woolbert, Richard
- Woods, Mrs. W. Kelly (Lydia)
- Woody, Ken
- Wooten, Richard "Boots"
- Workman, E.J.
- Work Study Programs
- Wright, Arthur F.
- Wright, Carolyne (2 Folders)
- Wright, Jack
- Writing Center
- Wylder, Erma
- Yancy, George R.
- Yearbook
- Yeend, Margaret (Peggy)
- Yenney, Mary Emma
- Young, Helen
- Young Democrates and Young Republicans
- Young, Merkin Sherman
- Zakariason, Kristine
- Zancker, Mrs. Huberta
- Zaring, Alice
- Zimmerman, Carroll Louis
- Zorb
- Science Outreach
- Women's Association for Self-Government